A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
- Artists' Files, bulk 1955-1999; circa 1907-2006; Series 3; 39.1 Linear feet Boxes 24-62, 95-96
  - Glarner, Fritz (Box 39)
    - Exhibition Catalog, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Lithographs, 1966-1982 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Mural, 1980-1983; 1970; 1960 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Mural at Nelson A. Rockefeller Residence, circa 1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Printed Materials, 1961-1964 (Box 39, Folder 21-22)
  - Glarner, Fritz, Publicity, circa 1949-1972 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Glasier, Marshall, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Glicenstein, Enrico, 1958-1962 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  - Glintenkamp, Henry J., 1960-1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Godfrey, Ian, Prices, Inventory and Consignments from I.G., 1994; 1987 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Godfrey, Ian, Reproductions, 1987-1991 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Goldhagen, Carl, 1992-1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Goldstein, Gladys, 1955-1959 (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
  - Goldthwaite, Anne, 1976-1983 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Goodwin, Richard La Barre, 1982; 1962-1968; 1975; 1909 (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
  - Gordon, Pat, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Gorey, Edward, 1968-1984 (Box 40, Folder 16-20)
  - Gorky, Arshile, 1959-1967 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Gossaert, Jean, undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Gould, Chester, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Gould, Chester, "Dick Tracy" (Sept. 14 - Oct. 9, 1982), 1979-1983 (Box 40, Folder 24-25)
  - Grace, Alexa, 1976-1982 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Grant, Dwinell, 1982-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Granville-Smith, Walter, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Graves, Nancy, To Be Re-Filed, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Groombridge, William, circa 1954 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Gross, Chaim, 1956-1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Gruger, F.R., 1977-1982 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Gruger, F.R. [Frederic], Traveling Exhibition, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Guerin, A.M., 1955 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Guerrero, Jose, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Guillemin [Empty Folder], circa late 1950s (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Gunn, Paul, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Guy, James, circa 1960s; 1983-1990 (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
  - Hague, Michael, 1980-1982 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Hancock Theodore, circa 1946-1959 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Harari, Hananiah, 1985-1990 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Harris, Lawren S., 1983-1989 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Harvey, James, 1958-1971 (Box 41, Folder 18-22)
  - Hasegawa, Keiko, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Haseltine, Herbert, 1972-1976 (Box 41, Folder 24-26)
  - Haupt, Theodore G., circa 1954-1956 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Hayes, Peter, Exhibition (1995) (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Hayes, Peter, Prices, Inventory and Consignments from P.H., 1988-1997 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Heade, Martin J., 1971-1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Heidenreich, Carl, 1959-1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Held, John, Jr., 1969-1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Herbert, David, 1970-1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Herzinger, Emil, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Heuston, 1980-1983 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Higgins, Victor, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Hiler, Hilaire, 1959-1960 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Hillsmith, Fannie, 1987-1992 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Hirshhorn, Joseph, 1957-1973 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Hoffman, Malvina, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Holden, Norman, undated; 1963-1967 (Box 42, Folder 13-14)
  - Holland, Harry, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Holland, Harry, Exhibition (Jan. 5-30, 1991), 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Holland, Harry, Photographic Materials, circa 1990 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Hollister, Paul, Jr., 1961-1964 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Holty, Carl, 1952-1973 (Box 42, Folder 19-20)
  - Holty, Carl (Box 42)
    - Archives, 1959-1991 (Box 42, Folder 21-22)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Lists and Receipts, 1982-1990 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Photographs, undated; 1980-1984 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Homer, Winslow, 1964-1968 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Hood, Dorothy, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Howard, Loretta, 1971-1972; 1960-1964 (Box 42, Folder 28-30)
  - Hoyland, John, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Hoyland, John (Box 42)
    - Biographical Information, circa 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Checklists, circa 1992 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Mailing List and Dinner List, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Press Release, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Slides and Transparencies, circa 1989-1992 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Hoyt, Dorothy, 1969-1970 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Hudson, Judith, circa 1993 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Hunt, William Morris, 1976; 1974 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Illustrations (Box 43)
    - (After 3), 1974-1983 (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
    - Becky's Illustration List, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 43, Folder 5-6)
    - Georgia, Gone, 1980-1982 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Georgia, Pending, 1972-1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Illustrations Sold (Photographs), undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Illustrators Show, 1971-1982 (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
    - Lists, 1970-1985 (Box 43, Folder 12-13)
    - "Little Nemo", 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Comics as of Sept. 1983 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Illustrations as of Sept. 1983 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1970s-1980s (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Price Lists, circa 1972-1981 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Illustrations and Comics, Consignments, 1976-1984 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Illustrations and Comics, Dead Memos and Receipts, 1976-1984 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Illustrations and Comics (Box 44)
    - Dead Memos and Receipts, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Dead Memos and Receipts (Comics), 1983 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - G.R. [Georgia Riley?], Miscellaneous, 1972-1983 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Memos, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Receipts, 1977-1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Indian, 1958-1960; undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, Ward, 1960s-1973 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - James, Charles, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - [James, Frederic], 1969-1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Janis, Maria Cooper, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 10-11)
  - Jaquette, Julia, circa 1997-1999 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Jayes, Bryn, circa 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 13-14)
  - Jensen, Alfred, 1960-1968 (Box 44, Folder 15-18)
  - Jimenez, Luis, 1968-1973 (Box 44, Folder 19-20)
  - Jones, Edward Powis, 1957; 1969-1973 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Jones, Thomas Dow (1809-1865), 1977-1981 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Jung, Simonetta Vigevani, 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Jung, Simonetta Vigevani, 1954-1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Jung, Simonetta Vigevani, Opening for March 14, 1955 Show (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Jung, Simonetta Vigevani, Photographs and Catalogs, circa 1950s (Box 45, Folder 3-5)
  - Kadish, Reuben, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Kaplow, Shana, 1996-1998 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Katz, Paul, circa 1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Keerl, Bayat (Box 45)
    - [Agreement], 1993 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Artists Accounting - Sold Invoices, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Correpondence, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - [Miscellaneous Administrative and Biographical], circa 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - "New Work" (May 2 - June 1, 1991), 1978-1993 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Kelly, Leon, 1963-1969 (Box 45, Folder 14-15)
  - Kidd, Jeremy, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Kirk, Elizabeth, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Klarwein, Mati, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 18-19)
  - Kline, Franz, 1962-1967 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Knight, Charles, 1950s-1971 (Box 45, Folder 21-22)
  - Koplin, Norma Jean, 1965-1970 (Box 45, Folder 23-24)
  - Krentzin, Earl, 1964-1968 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Kriesberg, Irving, 1951-1967 (Box 45, Folder 26-27)
  - Kriesberg, Irving (Box 46)
    - (I-II), 1955-1989 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
    - 1988 Exhibition, 1987-1989 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - [Artist Binder], circa 1980s (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - [Correspondence], 1980s (Box 46, Folder 5-6)
    - [Exhibitions], 1985-1989 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - [Inventory Cards], circa 1980s (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - [Photographic Materials], circa 1950s-1980s (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - [Press Binder and Administrative], 1980s (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Printed Materials, 1964; 1961 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - [Sales], 1984-1990 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Traveling, 1985-1987 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Krushenick, Nicolas, 1962-1965 (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
  - Kulicke, Robert, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Kupka, Frank, 1960-1978; undated (Box 46, Folder 17-18)
  - Kurhajec, Joseph, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - La Farge, John, 1965-1985 (Box 46, Folder 20-21)
  - Laing, Gerald, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Lataster, Ger, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Laufer, Miriam, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Lawroff, Nikolai Andrejevitch, undated (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Lawson, Ernest, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Lazzell, Blanche, 1985-1988 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Leaver, Tom, 1998-2004 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Lee, Jennifer, 1990-1996 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Lenson, Michael, Correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Lenson, Michael, Research Information, circa 1980s (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Lettick, Birney, 1969-1971 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Levine, Arthur, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Anthea, 1974-1977; 1986 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Norman, 1976; 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Linder, Jean, 1960s (Box 47, Folder 10-11)
  - Linder, Jean, Artist's Binder, circa 1964-1967 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Linhares, Judith, 1990s (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Lorentzen, Ida (Box 47)
    - Consignment Agreement, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Shipping, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Lumpkins, William, 1985-1988 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Macdonald-Wright, Stanton, 1955-1965 (Box 47, Folder 18-19)
  - Mager, Robert, 1973-1982 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Malicoat, Philip, 1963-1970 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Mangravite, Peppino, 1934-1979 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Mann, David, 1996-2000 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Manning, John, 1969-1979 (Box 47, Folder 24-26)
  - Marcus, Marcia, 1965-1967 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Maron, Jeffrey, 1980s (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Martin, Alexander, 1969-1978 (Box 48, Folder 2-3)
  - Martin, Charles, 1962; 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Martin, Keith, 1953-1960 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Massey, James, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Matulka, Jan (Van Loan), 1987-1996 (Box 48, Folder 7-8)
  - Matulka, Jan and Vaclav Vytlacil Exhibition (Oct. 20 - Nov. 14, 1992) (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Maurer, Lois (1832-1932), circa 1980s (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - May, Henry, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - McCall, Charles, 1956-1963 (Box 48, Folder 12-13)
  - McClanahan, Marion, 1968-1973 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - McFee, Henry, circa late 1950s (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - McKown, Richard, circa 1985-1991 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - McQuillan, Maureen, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Mead, Larkin, Research Done by Elizabeth Evens (More in Photo File), undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Meese, Bernard G., 1981 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Mejo, Oscar de, 1968-1976 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Melchers, Gari (Box 48)
    - Accounting, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Catalog, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1988 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence with Belmont The Gari Melchers Memorial Gallery, 1977-1979 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence with Clients and Lenders to Exhibition, 1978-1980 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Exhibition (1978) (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Exhibition and General Information (Sept. 26 - Oct. 28, 1978), 1974-1979 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Melchers, Gari, Exhibition and General Information (Sept. 26 - Oct. 28, 1978), 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Melchers, Gari, Miscellaneous, 1978-1979; 1988 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Meserve, Don Justin, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Meyer, Melissa, 1980s-1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Richard, undated; 1958-1960s (Box 49, Folder 5-6)
  - Miller, Richard, Biography, 1960-1963 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Mitchell, Lucy, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Miyashita, Tad, 1958-1962 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Mora, Luis F., 1911; 1962 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Moran, Thomas, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Moss, Tobey, 1981-1985 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Munson, Donald, 1969-1973 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Murphy, Stanley, Exhibition (May 20 - June 14, 1958), 1958-1960 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Nakian, Reuben, 1975-1978; 1966; 1969 (Box 49, Folder 15-16)
  - Nakoneczny, Michael (Box 49)
    - Artists Accounting - Sold Invoices, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - [Biographical Information and Press Binder], 1980s (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - [Consignments], 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - [Exhibition], 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - [Exhibition Postcards], 1988 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - [Photographic Materials], 1988-1991 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Press, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Namuth, Hans, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Neagle, John, undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Neel, Alice, circa 1981; undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Neel, Alice, Artist Binder, 1960-1970 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Neel, Alice, Exhibition Catalogs and Poster, 1963-1976 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Negret, Edgar, 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Negret, Edgar, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Nelson, Dianne, 1970-1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Newcomb, Mary, [Artist Binder], 1980s (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Newcomb, Mary, [Sales], 1994-1995; 1985-1987 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Newcomb, Mary and Dora Holzhandler (Dec. 11, 1985 - Jan. 11, 1986), circa 1984-1988 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
  - Newman, Robert Loftin, 1973-1976 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Nicholson, Rachel, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Oberteuffer, George, 1964-1972 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Oberteuffer, George (Box 50)
    - 1965 and 1978 Exhibitions, 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - General File, circa 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Photographic Materials, 1992; undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Oberteuffer, George and Henriette Amiard (Box 50)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1992 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence With Mrs. Betty Lee, 1990-1993; 1964-1984 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Letters of Agreement, 1975-1980; 1990-1992; 1965 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1981; 1964 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Oberteuffer, Henriette Amiard, Photographic Materials, undated; 1992; 1990 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Os, Georgius Jacobus Johannes van, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Pace, Stephen, 1962-1973 (Box 50, Folder 19-20)
  - Padovano, Anthony, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 50, Folder 21-23)
  - Padovano, Anthony (1979-1980) (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Padovano, Anthony (1981-1983), 1972-1983 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Pascal, David, 1972-1974 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Patrick, Rick (Box 50)
    - Artists Accounting - Sold Invoices, 1989-1991 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Consignments In/Out and Returned to Artist, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - [Essay], 1989 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1990-1992 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Paxton, William, 1941-1942; 1960-1968 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - Peale, Charles Willson, circa 1970s (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Perlis, Don, 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Phillips, Marjorie, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Pinkerton, Clayton, 1956-1960 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Plunkett, Edward, 1959-1974 (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
  - Poor, Anne, 1950s-1977 (Box 51, Folder 9-11)
  - Poor, Anne (Box 51)
    - Artist Binder, 1960s (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition (Feb. 13 - Mar. 6, 1968), 1962-1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - "Woman's Art Journal", 1982 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Poor, Henry Varnum, 1977-1983 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Potter, Mark, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Powell, Leslie, circa 1960s (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Prendergast, Maurice, "The Picnic" (1916), circa 1971 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Preston, James, 1964; 1959 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Preston, James, Exhibition (Nov. 17 - Dec. 12, 1964), 1968 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Price, Ursula Morley, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 21-23)
  - Price, Ursula Morley, Correspondence and Payments, 1982-1998 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Prince, Carolyn, 1955-1957 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Profile Press, 1969-1972 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - [Proctor, Alexander Phimister], circa 1994 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Pyle, Howard, 1982-1983; 1973-1975 (Box 51, Folder 28-29)
  - Quidor, John, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Quirt, Walter, 1955-1957 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Raimondi, John, 1984-1987 (Box 52, Folder 3-4)
  - Ramirez, E., 1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Ramirez, Eduardo, 1965-1966; 1963 (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
  - Ramirez Villamizar, Eduardo [and Edgar Negret and Gerald Gladstone], 1958-1965 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Ramos, Mel, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Ratton, Charles, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Reinhardt, Ad, 1960-1968 (Box 52, Folder 12-15)
    Oversized material housed in Box 96, Folder 2
  - Reisman, Philip, 1977-1980 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Remington, Frederic, 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Remington, Frederic, Bronzes, 1958-1970 (Box 52, Folder 18-21)
  - Renninger, Kathy S., 1955-1961 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Resika, Paul, 1967-1990 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Rie, Dame Lucie (Box 52)
    - Press, 1978; 1987-1995 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Prices, Inventory and Consignments from D.L.R., 1983-1996 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Printed Materials and Photographs, circa 1983-1990 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Reproductions, circa 1980s-1994 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Robins, Louisa, 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Rose, Herman, 1964-1965 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Rothstein, Barbarie, 1977-1979 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Roy, John, 1956-1957 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Ruddick, Dorothy, 1970-1975 (Box 52, Folder 32-33)
  - Ruddick, Dorothy, Artist Binder, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Russell, Alfred, 1955-circa 1960s (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Russell, Morgan, 1967; 1964 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Russell, Warren, Exhibition, 1958-1964 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
  - Ruta, Peter, 1972-1973; 1962 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Salemme, Attilio, 1955-1957 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Samant, Mohan, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Sandecki, Albert, 1960-1973 (Box 53, Folder 9-11)
  - Sandecki, Albert E. [and miscellaneous correspondence?], 1963-1971 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Santlofer, Jonathan (Box 53)
    - (1998), 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 13-14)
    - Biography and Press Release, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Clients, 1987-1989 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Consignments In, 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Consignments Out, 1988-1990 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (1-2), 1993-1997 (Box 53, Folder 19-20)
    - Correspondence Through 1993, 1988-1993 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - "Constructed Portraits" (Apr. 16 - May 14, 1994) (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition (Apr. 5-28, 2001) (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1983-2001 (Box 53, Folder 24-25)
    - Miscellaneous, 2004; 1988-1994 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Photos, 1990s (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Press, 1980s-1990s (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Santlofer, Jonathan (Box 54)
    - Press, 1980s-1990s (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Press and Exhibition Catalogs, 1983-1995 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Prints, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Returned to Artist, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Sales, 1987-1994 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Sales Invoices, 1986-1998 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Traveling, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - "Works on Paper" (Feb. 28 - Mar. 30, 1991), 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Sargent, John Singer, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Sargent, Winthrop, after 1965 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Schanker, Louis, 1981-1990 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Schapiro, Miriam, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Schildknecht, Edmund, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Schley, Reeve, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Schley, Reeve (Box 54)
    - (1982), 1982-1983 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - (1984), 1979-1986 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - (1999), 1999-2000 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Consignments In, 1989-1992 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Consignments Out, 1989-1995 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Corrrespondence, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence Through 1993, 1978-1991 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Exhibition (Apr. 5-28, 1990), 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition (Apr. 2 - May 2, 1992), 1990-1992 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition (1994) (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Exhibition (Apr. 15 - May 10, 1997), 1997-2000 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - [Financial Records], 1973-1996 (Box 54, Folder 27-28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1985 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Press, 1973-1995 (Box 54, Folder 30-31)
    - Receipts, 1994-1996 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Returned to Artist, 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Traveling, 1984-1986 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - "Watercolors" (May 4-29, 1976), 1976-1979 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Schmidt, Harold von, 1947; 1971-1974 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Schoonover, Frank, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Schumacher, William, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Schwabacher, Ethel, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - [Sculpture, Correspondence], 1983-1992 (Box 55, Folder 1-4)
  - Sculpture in Wood, 1973; 1964 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Segalman, Richard, 1963-1983 (Box 55, Folder 6-10)
  - Selz, Irma, 1971-1973; undated (Box 55, Folder 11-12)
  - Sennhauser, John, 1985-1988 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Sharp, William, 1940; 1969-1974; undated (Box 55, Folder 14-15)
  - Sherman, Pamela A. (Active 1860), undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Shulman, Morris, 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Simon, Sidney, 1949-1959; 1969-1975 (Box 55, Folder 18-19)
  - Slivka, David, 1963; 1960 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Slivka, David, 1961-1970 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Slivka, David, Publicity, circa 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Smart, Jeffrey, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Sommer, Billy, 1963-1964 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Sommer, William, 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Sorel, Edward, 1973-1982 (Box 56, Folder 6-8)
  - Southern Artists, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sparhawk-Jones, Elizabeth, 1983; 1963-1970; 1944 (Box 56, Folder 10-12)
  - Speight, Francis, 1979; 1974 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Spencer, Robert, 1923-1980 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Sprinchorn, Carl, 1922-1966 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Stair, Julian and Gabriele Koch, 1996-2000 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - [Stanley, John Mix], 1975 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Stein, Walter, 1964-1968 (Box 56, Folder 18-19)
  - Steir, Pat [and other "S" artists], 1962-1973 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    Oversized material housed in Box 96, Folder 3
  - Sterling, James, 1956-1964 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Stern, Lucia, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Stevens, Peter (Box 56)
    - Artists Accounting - Sales Invoices, 1985-1993 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Biographies, circa 1980s-1993 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Commissions, circa 1988 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Consignments (from Stevens) - Inventory, Prices, and Returned Works, 1989-1990 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Consignments In, 1990-1993 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Consignments Out, 1987-1992 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - "From the One to the Many" (Apr. 1 - May 1, 1993) (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - [Miscellaneous Exhibitions], circa 1985-1990 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Phillips Collection Exhibition (May 24 - Sept. 22, 1991), 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Stevens, Peter (Box 57)
    - Press and Printed Materials, 1983-1993 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Prices, circa early 1990s (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Returned to Artist, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Traveling, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Sugarman, George, 1955-1960 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Sully, Thomas, 1973-1976 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Sussman, Richard, 1955-1957 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Sutherland, Graham, 1993-1995 (Box 57, Folder 8)